<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>✊🏽 TRWBL 📺️</title>
      <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on ✊🏽 TRWBL 📺️</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>Escrow</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Escrow</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Escrow</guid>
    <description>One of the central questions for the courier network is how to prevent theft. This is accomplished by the distributor assigning a value to each parcel they ship &amp; before another party can take possession, they have to stake that assigned cost to be forfeit if they are found responsible for its loss.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 08:56:56 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Par</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Par</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Par</guid>
    <description>Goods and people are constantly being shuttled around by a set of couriering pairs. The software that is running in the vehicle is called Par. Depending on the situation, the two people in the car will fill a variety of roles.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 08:03:28 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Presidency</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Presidency</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Presidency</guid>
    <description>The calendars for the post-revolution era will kick off with the inauguration of a U.S. President.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 03:27:46 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Clock</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Clock</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Clock</guid>
    <description>Decimal Clock Time, for events organized by the revolution, are set to a ten-hour clock with a hundred minutes per hour and a hundred seconds per minute ...</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 02:48:34 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Calendars</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Calendars</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Calendars</guid>
    <description>Revolutionary Calendars There are two separate calendars used for organizing activities. Annual and holiday events are placed on a rotated 13-sign Sidereal Zodiac.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 02:34:46 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Norns</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Norns</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Norns</guid>
    <description>Users will create ordered lists which will be combined to produce new ordered lists personalized for individual users by Skuld, the fate concerned with the future ...</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 23:51:38 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Kaup</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Kaup</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Kaup</guid>
    <description>There is a huge quantity of unowned resources travelling through the couriers’ network. Kaup is the interface for users to describe their desires, peruse the available offerings and schedules, and to ultimately select what they want to receive.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 23:30:47 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Revolution</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Revolution</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Revolution</guid>
    <description>Funding Initially the funds to support the software development that is at the core of the revolution come from establishing a reliable and violence-averse market for all sorts of ...</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 23:15:32 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Týr</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/T%C3%BDr</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/T%C3%BDr</guid>
    <description></description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 07:15:30 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Hestia</title>
    <link>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Hestia</link>
    <guid>https://quartz.jzhao.xyz/Hestia</guid>
    <description>Hestia is a system for managing short term leases on specific locations targeted down to the level of a single room, or even piece of furniture. One of the initial testbeds will be the first Silver outpost.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 07:11:46 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>